thank you for coming to my session I a
感谢您参加我的会议
machine tomahto from Acropolis to Japan
从雅典卫城到日本的机器tomahto
I
一世
today I will give you a talk about let's
今天我会给你谈谈
visualize your spring Boudreau
可视化您的春天Boudreau
application about the visualization
关于可视化的应用
using less search or spinning travels
使用更少的搜索或旋转旅行
roost and zip King okay I will introduce
栖息地和拉链国王好，我将介绍
myself I am Xin tanimoto I'm I'm a
我自己是谷本新我是我
engineer of request technology in Japan
日本请求技术工程师
I'm a board member with Japan Japanese
我是Japan Japanese的董事会成员
the world it is Yu Jie Jie Zhao I am a
世界是玉杰杰赵我是
system architect and I'm a
系统架构师，我是
troubleshooter and now my current to
故障排除程序，现在我当前
historians current interest is micro
历史学家当前的兴趣是微观的
subsidies and elasticsearch I'm sure we
补贴和Elasticsearch我确定我们
are selling various technology and my
正在销售各种技术，我的
team is a mistake how many of you a
团队是一个错误，你们有多少人
mystic team mystic member no only one
神秘团队神秘成员只有一位
ok I will give you a talk about Pokemon
好吧，我会给你谈谈神奇宝贝
later then my my tutor Twitter account
稍后再我的导师Twitter帐户
is at mixology and my facebook is
正在调酒，而我的facebook是
shintali moto please follow me if you
新大利摩托，如果你，请跟我来
like it and before starting my session I
喜欢它，在开始我的课程之前
want to ask you to if you have any
想问你是否有
question ask me by Twitter or through I
问题通过推特或通过我问我
do
做
and the straightest event code is 5 4 6
最直接的事件代码是5 4 6
3 and Twitter hashtag with a sloppy and
3和Twitter标签，以及
cold VA s I will I'm gonna answer the
冷VA我会回答
questions after my session ok let's
会议结束后的问题好吧，让我们
begin
开始
it is said that seeing is believing but
据说眼见为实，但
injuria don't dare to believe this idiom
伤害不敢相信这个成语
something seemed deceiving or why so
似乎有些欺骗或为什么
think deceiving will see me pass reading
认为欺骗会让我通过阅读
or something then why do I say
那我为什么要说
visualizing is important because you
可视化很重要，因为您
can't even even believe if you see
甚至不敢相信你是否看到
nothing
没有
well you cannot persuade the passage
好吧，你不能说服通过
someone if you show nothing
一个人，如果你什么都不显示
so in the presentation you need
所以在演示中，您需要
presentation slides from your boss or
老板的演示幻灯片或
manager asks so easy a system is your
经理问这么简单，您的系统是
system work well or is there any
系统工作正常还是有
performance shortage or excess my amount
绩效不足或超出我的数额
of instances or easier in the in the
的实例或更容易
first place does the system contributes
系统贡献第一
to our business how will you answer the
对于我们的业务，您将如何回答
questions without the visualization will
没有可视化的问题将
you just open your web browser and
您只要打开网络浏览器，
access to your system and say everything
访问您的系统并说出一切
is fine the system works well or
系统运行正常还是很好
something I don't think so oh I I
我不这么认为的东西
understand that you will download the
了解您将下载
sub access log and read them all and to
子访问日志并全部读取它们并
confirm the system works well I don't
确认系统运作良好，我没有
believe it
相信它
yeah that's why you visualize your
是的，这就是为什么您形象化您的
system system per month or system health
系统每月系统或系统运行状况
you can explain the system health by
您可以通过以下方式解释系统运行状况
visualizing the server status and there
可视化服务器状态以及那里
is one more benefit can you visualize
你能想象得到的另一个好处
the system that is in sight you can get
可以看到的系统
insights from your visualization for
可视化的见解
example these are the famous diagram is
这些是著名的例子
called Esther you cannot see with some
叫做以斯帖，你看不到
score with service but it is yes you
服务得分，但是是的你
just knew that home it's complicated
只是知道家很复杂
muslim imagination that is inside well
内部的穆斯林想象力
if we visualize the cervix is lost by
如果我们看到子宫颈丢失
some means you might get an insight of
有些意思是您可能会了解
something to do with the business this
与业务有关
another reason is to be sure is this is
另一个原因是要确定这是
another reason to visualize your system
可视化系统的另一个原因
right then let's move on to the main
然后让我们继续前进
subject this is the star trying of my
主题，这是我的明星尝试
session
会议
here's a table of contents I'll explain
这是我要解释的目录
about the tools first and then ask for
关于工具，然后要求
questions are your server working well
问题是您的服务器工作正常吗
are your services in life comfortable
您的生活舒适吗
how do you micro-service look like and
您如何看待微服务以及
do us others contribute to your business
我们其他人对您的业务有贡献吗
another question is is it possible to
另一个问题是
talk about all of the topics in less
用更少的时间谈论所有主题
than 30 minutes okay let's go
超过30分钟，好吧，我们走
tools I will introduce three tools in
工具我将介绍三种工具
this session
本届会议
why is edible syllabus flood watch for
可食用课程大纲为何要注意
monitoring and a lot in and second one
监控以及很多第二
is elastic side through such pyramids
通过这样的金字塔是有弹性的一面
for monitoring and visualizing loans and
用于监控和可视化贷款以及
third white spring wealthiest and the
第三大白泉最富有和
king that is the main topic of this
国王，这是这个主题
session so this is for you did I really
会议，所以这是给你的，我真的
useful visualizing micro-services okay
有用的可视化微服务可以
do you know a diverse crowd watch
你知道各种各样的人群观看吗
is there anyone don't know crud watch
有没有人不认识克鲁德
everyone knows google it
每个人都知道谷歌
if you don't know it is okay it is just
如果您不知道可以的话
a kind of monetary - this is the
一种货币-这是
birthday monitoring services for a
生日监测服务
diverse the custom metrics not only the
多样化的自定义指标不仅
beauty matrix matrices but also custom
美容矩阵也可以自定义
metrics can be collected by either a CLI
指标可以通过CLI收集
where the base SDK on each server
每个服务器上的基本SDK
running on the each table and logs can
在每个表和日志上运行可以
be collected our also logs can be
收集我们的日志也可以
collected by ellebra slavs agent that is
由ellebra slavs特工收集
the agent to collect logs to send the
代理收集日志以发送
logs to the cloud watch server and the
记录到云监视服务器和
dog can be alternative how many of you
狗可以替代你们中的多少
are using data dog few of you and how
使用数据狗的人很少，以及如何
many of you are using cloud watch only
你们中的许多人仅使用Cloud Watch
are you ok I see
你知道吗
and this second tour is elastic such it
而第二次巡回演出是有弹性的
has excited obesity Bala beats this is a
兴奋的肥胖症
Cabana dashboard do you know how many of
Cabana仪表板你知道多少
almost all over you know elasticsearch
几乎所有人都知道Elasticsearch
yeah elasticsearch is full text of
是的elasticsearch是的全文
search engine and the log stash is a
搜索引擎，日志存储是一个
data collector and data processor and
数据收集器和数据处理器以及
also data sender to the receiver to the
也是数据发送者到接收者到
ask such and the Cabana is a
问这样，小屋是一个
visualization platform or for elastic
可视化平台或用于弹性
search and the beach is a newcomer that
搜索和海滩是一个新来的人
is the data simple letting go along and
是简单的数据吗？
this stock is so called blk stock or
这种股票被称为大宗股票或
stock Alec is the like this arm oh but
股票Alec就像这只手臂哦
it is a little although name so I know
虽然有点名字，但我知道
most of people called the lyric stock
大多数人称为歌词库
but because this is last as long as
但这是因为
Cabana but there is new comers beats so
小屋，但有新来者节拍，所以
how we can call call them lq p lv
我们怎么称呼他们lq p lv
the be with elk face away so now we can
与麋鹿面对面，所以现在我们可以
call them elastic stock this is the
称他们为弹性股，这是
option name
选项名称
I guess elastic people don't care about
我猜有弹性的人不在乎
the Google ability but the option name
Google功能，但选项名称
is rustic stock instead when someone is
是质朴的股票，而不是有人
sprinklers loose and jetking sprinklers
洒水喷头松动和喷水
is distribute tracing distributed
是分布跟踪分布
addressing system solution it put it to
解决它的寻址系统解决方案
put the colleague correlation ID which
把同事的相关ID
is a unique request ID commonly used in
是通常用于
micro services to process the request
微服务处理请求
the tourist idea is that the tour's ID
游客的想法是旅游的ID
is transmitted through the HTTP request
通过HTTP请求传输
header or a rabbit a McCue header or
标头或兔子McCue标头或
some kind of message headers and all of
某种消息头和所有
the micro services to process the
微服务处理
request knows the same correlation ID
请求知道相同的相关ID
in the through also embed the IDs into
在通行证中也将ID嵌入
the logs using SLA for JM DC and this is
使用SLA for JM DC记录日志，这是
map the map watch much diagonal nose
映射地图观看多对角线鼻子
Diagnostics the contagious okay I forgot
诊断我忘记的传染性好
the name sometimes so when you collect
有时候名字，所以当你收集
logs from sub several servers and you
从子几个服务器的日志，你
can find the logs long lines which are
可以找到日志长行是
related to the request by the treasurer
与司库的要求有关
ID using the correlation ID and also you
使用相关ID的ID，您也可以
can send the tourist data to zip king or
可以将旅游数据发送给zip king或
spring cross stream all right I will
春天横流我会的
explain it later on the other hand zip
另一方面，请稍后解释
King is a distributed dressing system
King是一个分布式敷料系统
server I think I can say that spring
服务器我想我可以说那个春天
cloud truth is the data collector or
云真相是数据收集器还是
data collection agent running with the
数据收集代理与
micro services and that K is a server
微服务，并且K是服务器
which collects the data from spring
从spring收集数据
classrooms
教室
okay do you have any question if you
好吧，你有什么问题吗
have asked me teacher was right okay so
问我老师是对的，所以
let's move on are your services working
让我们继续前进，您的服务是否正常运行
well how do you know so first of all you
好吧，你怎么首先知道
should monitor your servers newest
应该监视您的最新服务器
servers city usages memories and disc
服务器城市使用情况记忆和光盘
spaces and also you should monitor the
空间，您还应该监视
service processes that the process is
该流程是服务流程
working over stopped or the first check
工作停止或第一次检查
by HTTP call over something and put them
通过HTTP调用某些内容并将其放置
on the same dashboard
在同一仪表板上
putting them on the says same dashboard
将它们放在相同的仪表板上
is important to get to know the server
了解服务器很重要
status and services all over the
地位和服务遍布
services and also you should create a
服务，还应该创建一个
lot notification of them that's what it
他们的很多通知就是这样
like that actually this is my production
像这样，实际上这是我的作品
environment dashboards so I must some
环境仪表板，所以我必须
say some names I'm ask you some names
说一些名字我问你一些名字
there are CPU uses
有CPU使用
and CPU Christopher hands and disk space
和CPU Christopher的手和磁盘空间
available disk space uses memory arrival
可用磁盘空间使用内存到达
arrival IV availability and persist
到货IV可用性并持续
status is why do I have to do that one
状态就是为什么我必须这样做
reason is to see if servers are working
原因是看服务器是否正常工作
well now just now and second reason is
现在好，第二个原因是
to see if servers were working well in
看看服务器是否在
the past you should notice if server
过去，您应该注意服务器
down and recover last night was some
下来，昨晚恢复了一些
some time in the past and some reason to
过去的某个时间和某些原因
see if servers will be working well in
看看服务器在
the near future if the memory uses they
如果内存使用它们，不久的将来
are increasing or disk space disk
正在增加磁盘空间或磁盘
available spaces are decreasing
可用空间正在减少
you must increase them and to tell the
您必须增加他们并告诉
truth I sometimes didn't care about them
说实话我有时不在乎他们
and my server was down in production
我的服务器停产了
environment several times and how to do
环境好几次了，怎么办
you know I hope you already know to set
你知道我希望你已经知道要设定
up module interest it's very common
对模块的兴趣很普遍
sense and it's very famous but do you
感觉，它非常有名，但是你呢
know top the beach or elastic stock
知道海滩或弹性股票
do not talk a bit only one ok I will
不要只说一个就好
show you the top feet
给你看脚
top width is a data shipper for the
顶部宽度是
elasticsearch I will use this mirror
elasticsearch我会用这面镜子
display
显示
really
真
I forget something
我忘记了什么
okay this is a this was the top bid
好的，这是最高出价
this is a metric metric bid for no
这是不使用的指标出价
matter big bid now this is elastic
重要的出价现在这是有弹性的
version 5 alpha version so top bid is
版本5 alpha版本，因此最高出价是
now in the part of the metric beat but
现在是公制节拍的一部分
the function is saying there is a system
功能说有一个系统
loss or CPU uses these memory uses or
丢失或CPU使用这些内存使用或
disc spaces or something like that so
光盘空间或类似的东西
you can get system status or process
您可以获得系统状态或过程
status using top beat top bid is written
使用最高拍价最高出价记录状态
in go and easy to set up just run the
在运行中，易于设置，只需运行
process and it will collect data and zip
处理，它将收集数据和邮政编码
to the
到
elasticsearch it's very easy to set up
elasticsearch设置起来很容易
so I want you to use it ok let's go back
所以我要你使用它，好吧，我们回去
to the slides next question is are you
幻灯片上的下一个问题是你
associate enough comfortable what to do
联想足够舒适该做什么
so first of all you should monitor the
所以首先您应该监控
web access web access means you should
Web访问Web访问意味着您应该
monitor the public API access so that
监视公共API访问，以便
access coming to a response time
进入响应时间
palpable KPI and the response call
明显的KPI和响应调用
response status calls all of them are
响应状态的呼叫都是
200 to 500 400 over something and more
200至500400或更多
des des Vosges query count and query
des des Vosges查询计数和查询
response time this is the image of the
响应时间，这是图像
data monitoring the first line is the
数据监控的第一行是
average or blessed ones time by API such
API平均或祝福的时间
only there there are there is high peak
只有那里有高峰
in the past but ordinary is the column
过去，但专栏是普通的
and operate the second line is the
第二行是
average response time by API that is
API的平均响应时间为
that increases all the way pas des or
一路增加或
there also
还有
days there is a high peak but all of the
天有一个高峰，但所有的
time most of the time it is safe and the
大多数时间都是安全的
bottom line is access count PI API the
最重要的是访问计数PI API
these these these charts notice media
这些这些图表注意媒体
server status or process status and use
服务器状态或进程状态以及使用
the comfortability why do this to see if
舒适性为什么要这样做以查看是否
the visitor feel comfortable or get
访客感到舒适或感到
annoyed so how to do if you use ela or
惹恼了，所以如果您使用ela或
just use if you use the OB just use ELB
如果您使用OB则仅使用ELB
monitoring of the address crowd watch if
监视地址人群观看是否
you don't want if you don't or if you
如果你不想要或者你不想
want to know the know about PI API
想知道有关PI API的知识
status collect access logs using log
状态使用日志收集访问日志
stash or file Beach and forward them to
藏匿或归档海滩并将其转发给
elasticsearch and the visualize them on
elasticsearch并可视化它们
cabana then do the packet beat pocket
小屋然后做包拍口袋
beat is another data chipper Layton in
Beat是另一位数据削片者Layton在
gold like Wireshark over TCP dumped it
TCP上的Wireshark之​​类的黄金已将其丢弃
captures the network packets and analyze
捕获网络数据包并进行分析
them to obtain data this is the
他们获取数据，这是
screenshot of pocket beat it shows SQL
口袋拍子的屏幕快照，显示SQL
course or SQL response time lowest
课程或SQL响应时间最低
keywords
关键字
it is masked so you don't have to
它被遮盖了，所以您不必
install something some data source malte
安装一些数据源麦芽
you to you just install the packet beat
您到您只需安装数据包节拍
on your micro services so the micro
在您的微服务上
services use the network to access the
服务使用网络访问
data source so the packet beat captures
数据源，以便捕获数据包节拍
the network packet to create these
网络数据包来创建这些
matrix also it is easy to setup the next
矩阵也很容易设置下一个
one is the main topic how do you micro
一是主题你怎么微
subsidy look like what do do Torres
补贴看起来像做什么托雷斯
Microsoft Microsoft
微软微软
request by spring classrooms and
春季教室要求
centrist attitudes if King and visualize
国王和形象化的中间派态度
them why do this I do this to get a
他们为什么这样做我这样做是为了
grasp of your system look looks like and
掌握系统的外观看起来像
frame modifying something some Microsoft
框架修改一些微软
sees you should confirm the influence
看到你应该确认影响
range and also you can find the on usage
范围，您还可以找到使用情况
you use the service the next how to do
您使用服务接下来该怎么办
so go to spring initialize the website
所以去春天初始化网站
and find news and jib team and through
并找到新闻和臂架团队，并通过
dependencies add three dependencies to
依赖项添加了三个依赖项
your micro services and create Zipkin
您的微服务并创建Zipkin
sub using zip King dependencies so I
子使用zip King依赖项，所以我
know when you start something it is good
知道什么时候开始做某事是一件好事
thing to go to spring initializer but
要去Spring 初始化的东西，但
when you search crews in the spring
当您在春季搜寻工作人员时
initializer there are four serious
初始化器有四个严重的问题
things including two Zipkin something
东西包括两个Zipkin东西
and the feminist arts
和女权主义艺术
zip King on the on this side you will
在这边拉链国王
get another tooth dipped in something
再把一颗牙齿浸在某些东西上
okay I isomer I will summarize then into
好吧，我将异构体总结为
the one table through the definition
通过定义一个表
abstruse is spring clouds status roost
深刻的是春天的云状态栖身
in three stream with spring class you
在春季班的三流中
stream and this implant is sprinkle
流和这种植入物洒
status if King duplicate sorry with
状态，如果国王重复对不起
spring trowel is dipped in stream it's
春季抹子浸入溪中
hard to understand them so I will
很难理解他们，所以我会
explain them from the use case to stop
从用例中解释它们以停止
simply you have several micro services
只是您有几个微服务
and you won't ship the trace data to dip
而且您不会将跟踪数据发送到DIP
it in Sabah by HTTP the micro-services
通过HTTP在沙巴州的微服务
should have the dependency to dipped in
应该有浸入的依赖
client that fact ID is spring clouds
客户，事实ID是春天的云
start zipping it collects the data from
开始压缩它从中收集数据
the MA
硕士
services and sipped it two-zip kim and
服务，然后将其浸入两个拉链金和
on the other side saba side-zip Tainui
在另一边saba侧拉链Tainui
is a typical odd configure you are is a
是一个典型的奇怪配置，你是一个
ship can UI server and dip cassava that
船可以UI服务器和蘸木薯
is the story like a strange such engine
这个故事就像一个奇怪的引擎
is a ship in server and if you want to
是服务器中的船，如果您想
use RabbitMQ or Kafka in the middle
在中间使用RabbitMQ或Kafka
buffer you can use sprint cloud stream
可以使用sprint云流的缓冲区
something as a number of micro services
一些微服务
increases and they send lots of tourist
增加，他们吸引了很多游客
data to ship king the GPS server will
数据将向国王发送GPS服务器将
not be able to process them so over spec
无法处理它们，因此超出规范
then to prevent the zip-t server crash
然后防止zip-t服务器崩溃
you should use ship RabbitMQ or Kafka as
您应该使用RabbitMQ或Kafka作为
a meter buffer and even if Jimmy Saba is
一个仪表缓冲器，即使Jimmy Saba是
shut down or clashed over stopped la
关闭或发生冲突
veta make you can store that rest data
Veta使您可以存储其余数据
from the micro services and when dipkin
从微服务以及何时浸入
sub wake up Japanese ABBA will get the
子唤醒日本ABBA将获得
trace data from RabbitMQ if you want to
如果您想从RabbitMQ跟踪数据
create this environment these are the
创建这个环境是
answers on micro services subs inside
内部微服务订阅的答案
there you should you have to add the
在那里，您应该添加
dependency through stream and stream
通过流和流进行依赖
labid sirs dream is up is activist
激进的先生，梦想成真是激进主义者
spraying clouds will stream in spin
喷云会旋转
gravity the spraying class status women
重力喷涂班地位妇女
rabbit on the other hand the subside
另一方面兔子消退
depth in UI and deep history sprinkles
用户界面的深度和深厚的历史
with deeply stream and sprinkles that
与深流和洒
story M rabbit is also needed
故事M兔子也是需要的
you can substitute the sprinkles to bind
你可以用洒水代替
the rabbit for the spring crowds that
春天的兔子挤满了
assume rabbit it's enough I believe I've
假设兔子就足够了，我相信我已经
never tried what I think
从来没有尝试过我的想法
Kafka can be used for rabbitmq so with
Kafka可以用于Rabbitmq，因此
spring clouds dream by the Kafka the way
卡夫卡梦想的 Spring Cloud
you start the micro-services over
您重新开始微服务
chicken Sabah la botanicals exchange and
沙巴鸡肉植物交易所和
the cruise automated automatically
巡航自动自动
created so all the trace data is shipped
已创建，因此已发送所有跟踪数据
to the exchange named signals and
交换命名信号和
depakene server gets the trace data from
depakene服务器从以下位置获取跟踪数据
the cue name the sluice truths that is
提示名称是水闸真相
summarized series ended in dependencies
摘要系列以依赖关系结尾
if we use HTTP dipped in client is
如果我们使用HTTP蘸客户端
necessary for the client side and dipped
客户端需要，蘸
in you are and the jib gene server is
在你和臂架基因服务器是
necessary for the suicide and the when
自杀所必需的以及何时
you use mqp
你用mqp
through stream and so through stream is
通过流，所以通过流是
necessary for the client side and dipped
客户端需要，蘸
a stream and dipped in UI is necessary
流和浸入UI是必要的
for the server side and same lavage is
对于服务器端，相同的灌洗是
necessary for pause then what is this
暂停所必需的，这是什么
what is the sluice spring clouds that
水闸Spring Cloud是什么
tooth this is just add the trace and
牙齿，这只是添加痕迹，
spare IDs to the logs not it it doesn't
备用ID到日志，不是吗
have the ability to sit the data
有能力坐下来的数据
let's check the source code this is a
让我们检查一下源代码
jeepney server application to use HTTP
jeepney服务器应用程序使用HTTP
you just add the annotation enables you
您只需添加注释即可
to get server and run this application
获取服务器并运行此应用程序
to run the dip in server and if you want
运行浸入服务器，如果你想
to use the rabbitmq or Kafka in the
在中使用rabbitmq或Kafka
middle buffer like like three you just
像三个一样的中间缓冲区
add the this annotation enable Japanese
添加此注释启用日语
stream server and on the other hand the
流服务器，另一方面
client-side no source code modification
客户端无源代码修改
is necessary for the micro service
微服务所必需的
this okay let's take a brief demo we I
好的，我们来做一个简短的演示
just have five minutes
只需五分钟
here is a sample sample application
这是一个示例应用程序示例
fitting in spring and spring crowds like
适合春季和春季人群喜欢
e-commerce site the example let's run
电子商务网站的示例让我们运行
this test this test called the show
这个测试叫做show
catalog so access to get the data from
目录，以便从中获取数据
the catalog and and put the items into
目录，然后将项目放入
the cart and get the card again and
购物车，然后再次获取卡，
order checkout when I run this test
我运行此测试时的订单结帐
just finish
刚完成
and find them in Zipkin store service
并在Zipkin商店服务中找到它们
store services from like BFF find traces
像BFF这样的商店服务找到踪迹
you can see the - you can see the you
你可以看到-你可以看到你
can finds the bottleneck or some
可以找到瓶颈或一些
response response time and bottlenecks
响应时间和瓶颈
from this chart and you can also find
从此图表中，您还可以找到
the dependencies of the services no stop
服务的依赖性永无止境
is called the stocks our agenda item
被称为股票我们的议程项目
service and when I check out I pass to a
服务，当我结帐时，我会通过
service called the order service and
服务称为订单服务，
order all the service called the stop
订购所有叫停的服务
service car service payment service I
服务车服务付款服务我
have no time
没有时间
note that sprinkles does not support
请注意，不支持洒水
gravity right
重力权
this is crust including the spring boots
这是外壳，包括 spring boot
that AMQP its spring classes suppose
AMQP的春季班
stream rabbits sprinkles start a stream
流兔洒开始流
rabbits so if you are using mqp were la
兔子，所以如果您使用的是mqp
you are using RabbitMQ you shouldn't use
您正在使用RabbitMQ，您不应该使用
the spring boots tatah MTP you should
spring boot 塔塔MTP，你应该
use sprinkles that a streamer Abbott
用洒的流光雅培
okay I have no time more so there is
好吧，我没有时间了，所以有
another chapter on but I will give this
另一章，但我会给这个
ride after this session so last one is I
会议结束后骑车，所以我是最后一个
committed the sample code in the github
在github中提交了示例代码
and all the creepers downloaded by
以及所有由下载的爬虫
Austria in Japan so thank you very much
奥地利在日本，非常感谢
for coming my session thank you very
参加我的会议非常感谢
much if you have a question come after
如果您有任何疑问，请多多关注
this session thank you
本届会议谢谢